triabeauty.com 2012-05-08

# TRIA Beauty Customer Care - Visit TRIA Customer Care

**YOUR PRIVACY AND THE SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IS VERY IMPORTANT TO US**

This Privacy Policy governs your use of triabeauty.com and trytrialaser.com (the "Site"). TRIA Beauty values our customers and guests and respects your concerns about online security and privacy. We believe in providing you with a safe and secure online experience. Our Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with information about how TRIA Beauty collects and handles information about you, including your personal information on the Site. By using our Site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as set forth herein. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Terms of Use by this reference. In addition to reviewing our Privacy Policy, you should also read our Terms of Use. Your use of the Site constitutes your agreement to the terms and conditions in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.  

**OUR PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY WILL CHANGE OVER TIME**   
Because we continue to develop the Site and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, our policies will change over time. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy from time to time to stay abreast of our most current privacy policy practices. Your continued access and use of the Site will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to our Privacy Policy.   

**SUMMARY OF OUR PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY**   
This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and protect your personal information as you interact with us online. This Privacy Policy explains:  

  * What information TRIA Beauty gathers from users of the Site.
  * How TRIA Beauty uses the personal information that you share with us and that we learn about you because of our relationship.
  * How TRIA Beauty uses non-personal information. 
  * What personal information, if any, TRIA Beauty may share about you with others and the conditions that protect your information if it must be shared.
  * What kind of security measures TRIA Beauty takes to protect your information from loss or disclosure.
  * The circumstances under which you can access personal information you have shared with TRIA Beauty and have that information corrected, restrict TRIA Beauty's use of that information, and even have it removed from our active servers. 
  * Other things you should know about privacy and TRIA Beauty.

**THE TYPE OF INFORMATION THE SITE COLLECTS ABOUT YOU**  
TRIA Beauty collects information that you provide to us or that we learn about you from your use of the Site. For example, you may provide information to the Site when you register, sign in, search, add items to your shopping cart, participate in a survey, rate or review our products or services, or communicate with TRIA Beauty's Customer Care department online. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and personal shopping and product preferences. We also automatically receive and store certain types of non-personal information, such as demographic or statistical information, whenever you visit the Site.

**  
HOW TRIA BEAUTY USES AND SHARES INFORMATION ABOUT YOU**   
We try to provide you with the information you need to make informed, reasonable choices with respect to how the Site uses or shares your information. TRIA Beauty uses and shares personal information from you in several ways:

We use information we have collected about you to provide you with the very best health and beauty news, products and services, and shopping experience and to operate our business. We do not sell your personal information to third parties for any reason. We do not disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties who may want to offer you their own products and services unless you have requested or authorized us to do so. 

We may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of TRIA Beauty where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction or do something you have asked us to do. Likewise, we may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of TRIA Beauty with whom we have contracted to perform services on our behalf. Companies that act on our behalf are required to keep the personal information we provide to them confidential and to use the personal information we share only to provide the services we ask them to perform. 

We may disclose your personal information as permitted or required by law, such as in connection with a subpoena or similar legal process, or in connection with a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy, as discussed further below.

**  
WEBSITE USAGE**   
TRIA Beauty or its authorized service providers may observe activities, preferences and transactional data (such as your IP address, browser type and operating system) relating to your use of the Site. This information is generally collected in non-personally identifiable format. We may use this collected or logged information in order to provide better service, to facilitate our customers' use of the Site, to track usage of the Site, to address security hazards, and for other administrative or operational purposes. TRIA Beauty, or its authorized service providers, may use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout the Site. We may use aggregated, statistical information to describe our customer audience, products, and services, and to develop partnerships with third parties to offer products and services in which we believe our customers will be interested.

**  
ONLINE TRANSACTIONS**   
We collect information, including personal information, about you when you use our Site. For example, to open an account with us, you will need to provide us with certain information, including your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address. If necessary, we will assist you in creating a user ID and a password. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your log-in information and password. When you request to purchase items in your shopping cart, we will forward your request and basic account information to the e-commerce service provider. When you provide personal financial and other personal information to the service providers featured through the Site, the sales transaction will occur on the service provider's site and not on the Site. As such, any financial and personal information you provide in placing your order is controlled by and governed by the privacy policy of that service provider.

 **  
CONTENT YOU SUBMIT FOR POSTING**  
Some content that you post on the Site, for example when you share your experiences or rate or review products or services, may be made publicly available on the Site, in print or on third party websites and social media. If you would like to give us feedback on a product or service in a non-public manner, please contact us directly using the contact information below in the "Questions or Comments" section. 

**  
OUR SECURITY PRACTICES**   
Except as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy, our internal data security policies restrict access to customers' personal information to authorized employees for TRIA Beauty business purposes only. Our employees are bound by TRIA Beauty policies that require them to maintain the confidentiality of our customers' personal information. Employees who violate these requirements are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that are designed to guard our customers' personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, TRIA Beauty cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk.

**  
WHAT ARE COOKIES AND HOW DOES THE SITE USE THEM?**   
We may use cookies to collect or log certain information. A cookie is a small piece of information that a Site stores on a personal computer and which it can later retrieve. We may use cookies for some administrative purposes, for example, to store our customers' preferences for certain kinds of products or to store a password so that you do not have to input it every time you visit our Site. The cookies will not contain personal information that will enable anyone to contact our customers via telephone, email, or other means. If our customers are uncomfortable with the use of cookie technology, they can set their browsers to refuse cookies. Certain services, however, could be dependent on cookies and our customers may disable those services by refusing cookies.

**  
LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES**   
The Site may contain links to third-party sites. Please be aware, however, that TRIA Beauty is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy policies of these other sites or their practices. We encourage you to read the privacy policies for these other sites, as they may differ from ours. This Site may also contain links to sites that display TRIA Beauty branding and/or TRIA Beauty's logo but which are maintained by third parties. Such websites are identified as third party sites by the website address or URL because they do not display a triabeauty.com URL. Please read the privacy policy on these sites for applicable privacy practices relating to personal information collected via the sites because they may differ from the Site's privacy practices. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by TRIA Beauty via the Site. 

**CONTACT PREFERENCES AND ACCESSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**   
You have choices when it comes to how TRIA Beauty uses your personal information. When you register online with or purchase items from the Site or otherwise provide your email address to us, you are automatically signed up to receive information about merchandise, services and special promotional offers from us by e-mail and/or direct mail. If you do not wish to receive such product marketing information, please contact us by e-mail or direct mail to unsubscribe at [customercare@triabeauty.com](mailto:customercare@triabeauty.com) or TRIA Beauty, 4160 Dublin Blvd., Suite 200, Dublin, CA 94568. If you have an account on the Site, you can also change your contact preferences at any time by following the instructions on the Site. If you elect not to receive such product marketing information, TRIA Beauty may continue to contact you as necessary to service your account and process your transactions and requests. 

Keeping your account information accurate and up-to-date is very important so we can provide you with excellent service. If your account information is incomplete, inaccurate, or not current, please follow the instructions on <http://www.triabeauty.com/login.htm> on the Site to correct your account information online.

(For California Residents), California Privacy Rights under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84: California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84 give California residents the right to ask us for a notice describing the categories of personal information we share with third parties or affiliates for their direct marketing purposes. The notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it has been shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to [customercare@triabeauty.com](mailto:customercare@triabeauty.com) or TRIA Beauty, 4160 Dublin Blvd., Suite 200, Dublin, CA 94568. Please allow 30 days for a response. 

**  
THIS PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY APPLIES TO U.S. CUSTOMERS**   
The Site is hosted in the United States and is intended for U.S. visitors. This Privacy Policy applies to residents of the United States. Parts of this Privacy Policy may not apply to visitors outside the United States. If you are a non-U.S. visitor to our Site, by visiting our Site and providing us with data, you acknowledge, agree and provide your consent that your personal information may be processed in the United States for the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction, which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own. By using this Site and providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.

**MERGERS, ACQUISITIONS, AND BANKRUPTCY**  
If TRIA Beauty should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, or if TRIA Beauty should decide to buy another business, or sell or reorganize part or all of TRIA Beauty's business, TRIA Beauty may be required to disclose your personal information to prospective or actual purchasers and other parties. It is TRIA Beauty's practice to obtain appropriate confidentiality protections for information disclosed in these types of transactions.

**  
TRIABEAUTY.COM IS NOT FOR USE BY CHILDREN**   
The Site is not intended for use by minor children (under the age of 18). Parents and guardians should monitor the use of the Site by minor children. Children under age 13 should not use the Site at all. If a child under age 13 submits information through any part of the Site, and TRIA Beauty becomes aware that the person submitting the information is under age 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. 

**  
WHAT ELSE SHOULD I KNOW ABOUT MY PRIVACY?**   
You should be careful to maintain the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information and be responsible about protecting your personal information and identity whenever you are online.

**  
QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS**   
TRIA Beauty is committed to quality customer experience. If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by:  

  * Sending us an e-mail or contacting our Customer Care department at [ customercare@triabeauty.com](mailto:customercare@triabeauty.com); or 
  * Writing to us at: 

TRIA Beauty  
4160 Dublin Blvd., Suite 200  
Dublin, CA 94568 

**LAST REVISED** January 18, 2011
